<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>unpublished on Blake Bronson-Bartlett</title>
    <link>http://example.org/categories/unpublished/</link>
    <description>Recent content in unpublished on Blake Bronson-Bartlett</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/unpublished/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Conferences</title>
      <link>http://example.org/conference_presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/conference_presentations/</guid>
      <description>Conferences Talks &amp;ldquo;The Pencil&amp;rsquo;s Progress: A Defense of Messy Handwriting.&amp;rdquo; Day at Dumbarton (The National Society of the Colonial Dames of America/Dumbarton House, Washington, D.C.), Virtual, April 28, 2022.
Delivered Papers &amp;ldquo;The Wild Traces of Calaveras County in Notebook IV.&amp;rdquo; The 8th Annual Quarry Farm Symposium: Mark Twain and the West, Elmira, NY, October 1-3, 2020.
“Graphite’s Dirty Truth: The Pencil in Whitman’s New York Poetry.” International Whitman Week 2019, Walt Whitman &amp;amp; New York Symposium, The Grolier Club, June 1, 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Projects</title>
      <link>http://example.org/digital_projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/digital_projects/</guid>
      <description>Digital Projects &#34;Mabbott Poe: A Digital Resource for the Study of Edgar Allan Poe and the Editing of his Collected Writings by Thomas Ollive Mabbott.&#34; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>http://example.org/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>http://example.org/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/publications/</guid>
      <description>Publications Book Chapters &amp;ldquo;Graphite Time.&amp;rdquo; Handwriting in Early America: A Media History. Ed. Mark Alan Mattes. Amherst: University of Massachusetts Press (in press).
Peer-reviewed Academic Articles &#34;The California and Hawaii Notebooks: Pencils, Pocket Notebooks, and the Messiness of Mark Twain.&#34; Mark Twain Annual 20 (2022). &#34;The Mysterious Stranger’s Crisis of Duplicates: Incompletion and the Vexed Transmission of Twain&#39;s Late Writings.&#34; Mark Twain Annual 18 (2020). “Writing with Pencils in the Antebellum U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>http://example.org/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Teaching Visiting Assistant Professor, University of Iowa, Iowa City, IA, 2016-2019. Breaking Form/Making Books: Literary Experimentation in the US after 1800, University of Iowa, Iowa City, IA, Visiting Assistant Professor, 2019, 1 section. This course consisted of three five-week units based on the study of single authors who were considered innovators in their own time: Walt Whitman, Langston Hughes, and Ronald Johnson. Each unit began with a session working with rare editions of the authors’ works in the university’s special collections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Translations</title>
      <link>http://example.org/translations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/translations/</guid>
      <description>Translations With Robert Fernandez. Morisseau-Leroy, Félix. Antigòn (excerpt). Intranslation. September 2017.. Stingelin, Martin. &amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;Writing&amp;rsquo;: An Introduction.&amp;rdquo; In &amp;ldquo;I am disgusted with this century of scribblers&amp;rdquo;: Writing Scenes in the Age of Manuscript&amp;rdquo; [“‘Schreiben’: Einleitung.” In “Mir ekelt vor diesem tintenklecksenden Säkulum&amp;rdquo;: Schreibszenen im Zeitalter der Manuskripte]. Ed. Martin Stingelin. Munich: Wilhelm Fink. 7-21. PDF Mallarmé, Stéphane. Azure: Poems and Selections from the “Livre.” With Robert Fernandez. Middletown, CT: Wesleyan University Press, 2015.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>